Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
In the second round of the Royal Knights selection exam, Longress' Team G won by a slim margin.
Finral, no!
However, even after the match was over, the crazed Longress continued to attack his older brother Finral.
Disappear.
The other Black Bulls stepped in to save their wounded comrade.
Hey!
Go on, take one more step toward him.
But you should know that the second you do, you're dead.
You Black Bulls may be doing better than expected, but you're still worthless underlings.
You think you could take the Vice-Captain of the Golden Dawn?
Your vrink has nothing to do with this.
All we care about is protecting our friend.
You may have lucked out and failed upward to get to this point, but you're still a nobody who's talking to someone completely out of your league.
Wizard King, before the next teams face off against each other, allow me to put these Black Bulls in their rightful place.
In fact, the fight can start now! Let the semi-finals begin!
Wizard King, sir. You're not going to stop them?
If this were an actual battle, no one would be able to control when the fighting begins or ends.
Longress' sudden violent outburst forced teams B and G into an impromptu semi-final face off.
But part of Julius' plan for this test was to expose an involuntary traitor working on behalf of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Asta, no!
In order to subdue Longress, Asta called upon his Black Asta form.
How about some help, Zerks?
Focusing his might, he put his trust in the mage called Zerks.
Look at him, smirking with all the confidence in the world.
Whose real name was Zora.
Damn it.
I swear I'll use the power I possess and protect everyone who needs my help.
That's my duty as a magic knight.
Zora's father, Zora, was the first commoner to become a magic knight.
However, he was eventually betrayed by his own squad mates and murdered.
You jerks!
My father knew what a knight should be!
And you are no magic knight!
You BO it!
I only不能 say it again its way to one another one.
You can say it even better.
How do I know?
I don't understand you, game inconvenient, right?
That means it's everything you've heard.
I'm building a lot more都是 seed.
이라고 SecurityJean
This story every time celle ties the wallet
right here and the best
When Bodger is open on my own
or should I call her
But I see the baby
Me and the girl
A child
She's mysterious
Music
.
Be gone! I am the true magic knight here!
He broke through the circle!
Careful, Zax!
Congrats on being the first one to hit me today, snot-nosed royal.
What?
A magic circle on his body?
I don't believe my eyes!
Casting a spell like that over his own body, that'll be a constant drain on his power.
Not to mention it's an extremely risky strategy.
I agree, it is rash.
But then, that does appear to be the way he operates.
Whoa, there's no way!
Impossible!
What have you done?
Who the hell are you?
Oh, no one in particular.
Just a living embodiment of the anger of a filthy brat from some poor village.
Have a little taste of my rage!
Pathetic excuse for magic knight!
He just reflected that spatial magic!
But that will only double his power!
I refuse to let some nobody toy with me!
He'll pay for this!
Fuck!
What happened to that attack after he doubled its strength?
He made it go away!
The vice-captain was powerful before, but this is something else entirely.
Where is all this magic coming from?
Your highness.
Yeah.
As it turns out, not even your little ace in the hole was enough to slow me down to the slightest!
All you did was give me more to work with!
It's just as I've been telling you all along, I really am special!
Unlike my weak brother, and unlike you as well!
All of you are so pathetic, nothing you do will amount to anything!
Wanna bet!
How dare you!
Go away, Royal. I don't need your stupid healing spell, so stop!
That's out of the question!
Not only are we on the same team, you and I are both magic knights!
What did you just do? Your appearance changed!
Oh, it's really nothing special! This is just what happens when a commoner gets tired of hearing all your trash talk!
Everywhere I turn, I see yet another nuisance to contend with!
So do try to stay out of my portals during the next battle. It would be a shame if you were to permanently disappear somewhere.
Forget about what it would do to mother and father, I think a certain someone would be quite devastated as well.
Yeah, good point.
So if I want to prevent that, then I'll just have to win.
Despite knowing I'm a chosen one, you would still dare think you are my equal?
Nobles! I am one of a kind! You don't stand a chance against my supreme greatness!
Yeah, right. You are something else.
Even as nobles go, your power is crazy intense.
Your spatial magic is off the charts.
You were born incredible.
That was what I always wanted! To be someone special!
I've fought alongside a real tough character on the battlefield today.
He definitely knew impressive ways to use time magic.
Your power may be awesome, but you know what really sets us apart?
I don't care whether you're impressed with me or not.
I mean, I can't stand you!
Just... don't take him from us for nothing!
Unlike you, we don't want to be powerful just to get our way.
We use magic to protect each other.
We compete so we can all get better!
We fight as a team.
That's the only reason we've made it this far!
I've heard enough!
If you wanted to live, you should have groveled at my feet or kept your commoner mouth shut!
Good for nothing, Kurt!
You can call me names all day long, but you won't be laughing when you see my power!
I'll burn it into you!
My magic's not working!
I lost death.
Black meteorite!
I've heard enough!
If you wanted to live, you should have groveled at my feet or kept your commoner mouth shut!
Good for nothing, Kurt!
You can call me names all day long, but you won't be laughing when you see my power!
I'll burn it into you!
My magic's not working!
Black meteorite!
Both crystals broke at the same time!
This match is a draw!
Oh my goodness!
He's out cold!
That was a Flaholus defeat!
I see!
As long as you've got the advantage, that means you're always in the right, does it?
Mr. Fancy Pants Nobleman?
If so, now that you've had your ass handed to you by a commoner, I guess that puts you in the wrong.
Anyway, after that little tantrum, nobody's ever gonna let you be their vice-captain again.
Hey, fluffy hat girl!
What were you even doing during that last battle?
So scared of Portal Boy that you had to wait on the sidelines?
Must've been nice to kick back, huh?
Listen, there's no reason for you to be such a jerk about it!
Shut your trap!
Why would I care what a no-talent show off like you thinks?
You types are the most useless ones of the bunch, and we both know it's true!
Quit the Magic Knights and go home already, you trash!
And Shorty!
You gotta stop putting so much trust in everybody who comes your way!
Not everyone's a good guy, and the good ones ain't that good!
You're gonna end up getting yourself killed!
Please don't say that!
As for you, you're always trying to act according to what's best for the given circumstances.
But you better be careful!
Don't throw thinking out the window entirely when there's a situation you weren't anticipating!
Little Miss Royal.
Do you have dead?
And you!
Yeah, you!
The devilishly handsome guy with the awesome mask!
If you ask, you should have depended on your teammates a whole lot more.
Draw. We didn't win.
Man, I hate this.
Let's do our best out there, everyone.
No matter what, we're all Magic Knights of the Clover Kingdom!
The fight ended in a draw, between your brothers and Asta's teams.
But our showing was better.
The newbie superstar of the Black Bulls giving the Vice-Captain of the Golden Dawn a run for his money made a pretty big impression.
Which is why, you need to hurry and wake up soon.
While you've been here resting up, our friends have been accomplishing some great things.
I've administered first aid, but his wounds are too serious.
Let's take him to the infirmary.
Cobb, do you mind?
Don't mind it one itty bitty bit, sir!
Then I'll be going with you.
It looks like your team is on deck.
You better not screw it up.
Yeah, I got this!
Next, we'll continue on with Team I, Rill, Mills, and Ruben.
Versus Team K, Pulley, Klaus, and Luck.
Round two, match three will begin momentarily.
Oh, yeah!
Let's hit them with everything we've got, fellas!
Well, we're up against the Captain of the Aqua Deer.
He'd just counter every attack with its direct weakness.
What to do?
I think I might have a good strategy.
Wanna hear it?
I can't wait to see what kind of masterpiece I'm going to create this time!
If we provide enough backup, we might win!
Huh?
That magic.
Someone's condensing it and making it more refined!
There's no point in countering an ultra-fast attack spell.
One strike and he's toast!
I guess we're kind of copying the combo spells those other guys were using in the first round.
But I bet you this technique is going to have a lot more oof to it!
That looks bad.
We've got to get our team's crystal to safety!
Don't bother moving out of the way!
On a battlefield like this, I'll always know exactly where you're hiding!
Oh, wow!
I'm sure it travels really fast!
Better get to drawing, then!
Whatever your next move is, it won't help you at all!
Cause this spell pierces through everything!
Ha, ha, magic!
Lightning arrow!
Nobody's gonna stop this attack!
He's right!
Picture magic!
Game of the gods!
Actually, I drew a little inspiration from the first round myself.
The method's not quite the same.
But I'm still charging up the enemy's spell!
And reflecting it!
Welp!
Crystal destroyed!
Team Eye wins!
What in the world just happened here?
Uh, your guess is as good as mine.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Well, he's not the captain for nothing!
Wow, that was so good!
That's real boy mortier for you!
And I got a glimpse of my great masterpiece!
Woo-hoo!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Oh, boy.
That didn't last very long.
Shake it off, you guys!
Excuse me, Black Bulls?
It's Asta. He's severely exhausted now.
We took him to the infirmary downstairs.
I'm going to stay with him for a while.
Please be here for Noelle in my stead.
The next matchup is Team M, Ben, Brad, and Eric
versus Team P, N, Noelle, and Yuno.
Stand by for Round 2, Match 4.
This is for Asta.
I'm going to fight for everyone who's lost
and definitely not one specific person!
Of course we are.
And we're going to win.
Round 2, Match 4, begin!
Hey! Don't just go without me!
I refuse to waste my time standing still.
There they are!
Just him?
Who is this guy?
Begone!
Wind magic!
Towering Tornado!
What the?
But...
He's nothing but a Kamala!
Asta.
You may be down, but you'll get back up.
I've seen how quickly you adapt and improve.
The more it hurts, the further you push yourself.
Soon you'll be countless times stronger than you are now.
You may be down, but you'll get back up.
I'm coming out...
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Uh, crystal destroyed!
Team P wins!
What did he just do?
And how?
Oh, man.
That spell was pretty damn sweet.
Yeah, I wish I could fight him, too!
You know. I can see that you've got much more to show us.
You know? What's your problem finishing them all up by yourself?
I wish you'd use my power every once in a while! My talents are wasted on you!
Shut up.
Ah! You sure stress me out! I don't hate that about you, though.
Next up, match two of the semi-finals.
But it will be much more than that.
Since the first match of this round resulted in a draw,
this face-off between Team I and Team P is going to be the last bout of our great tournament.
Asta, I'm moving forward.
We'll be right back.
Thank you so much for watching.
Faster.
Not a single one of us has any magic ability, but no matter what, we still never give up on our treats.
Sister Lily is so gonna marry me!
Me.
Me!
We'll fight for it!
Yeah!
Sure, we may argue sometimes, but we'll always be a family!
One of them is a racket, but five is enough to drive you up a damn wall.
Yeah, one is plenty.
It's finally time for the deciding match.
I really did enjoy seeing all those different spells in action.
I don't want it to end yet!
Black Clover page 84, the victors.
Now let's see which team of Magic Knights will take home the glory.
Now let's see which team of Magic Knights will be on the autfare.
You